ALABI, TOYIN BUKOLA

12, Oladejo Street, Kajola-monatan; Iwo road. Ibadan

① 09096626616, 08069513575 **②** Alabitoyin0806@gmail.com

Gender: Female Marital Status: Single State of Origin: Oyo state Nationality: Nigeria

PROFILE

Bukola is a competent customer service representative and administrative professional with over 2+ years' combined experience in office administration, executive support, customer/vendor relationship and sales alongside passion for efficient office management. She is seeking to leverage her administrative skills in an administrative-related position. Previously, she has planned, designed, and developed office operations - resulting in 18% uplift in efficiency. At the last firm she worked for, she planned workforce usage, space requirements, and office layouts to optimize workflows which led to 10% increased workflow.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Microsoft Office Suite
- Communication & Interpersonal Skills
- General Administration
- Solid Works
- Office Administration
- Organizational Strategic Support
- Influence and Negotiation

- Planning and Prioritization
- Advisory Assistance
- Attention to Detail
- Collaboration
- Customer Service
- Data Gathering and Analysis

CAREER SMMARY/ACHIEVEMENTS

- 2+ years' combined experience in office administration, customer relationship and sales
- Customer Care Agent, Nellobyte Limited Nigeria
- Corporate Sales Executive , Globacom Nigeria
- Administrative/Sales and Marketing Officer, 4TSM Farms
- Administrative Officer (NYSC), College of Education
- Resolved an average of 50 inquiries in any given week and consistently met performance benchmarks in all areas (speed, accuracy and volume) at 4TSM Farms
- Created a more efficient Word database for forms, letters and documents, which decreased production time by 20%.
- Promoted company and increased sales by coordinating and attending trade shows.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Care Agent

Nellobyte System Limited, Ibadan

December 2018 - Till date

Key Responsibilities:

Co-ordination and escalation of related calls to the authorities and follow up for resolution

Maintaining relationship with new and existing customers during complaints, enquiries and request.

Having detailed knowledge of the client's needs and then customizing the product/ services as per their needs Physical contacts with customers for various sim registrations, sim activation and airtime, data/various sim bonus activations

Checking out customer's tickets for complains, enquiries, or request and proffering solutions to them hence resulting in customer's satisfaction and company development

Corporate Sales Executive

GlobalCom, Ibadan

June 2018 - December 2018

Key Responsibilities:

Contributes to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed

- Keeping records/logs of all sales
- Researching and identifying sales opportunity, generating leads, target identification and classification
- Reaching out to new customers and making presentations or pitches outlining the benefits of product/ services.
- Understanding the client requirements and then customizing the product/ services as per their needs
- Maintaining relationship with all potential and existing clients
- Ensuring proper servicing and after sales support to clients
- Data reporting to management and gathering market intelligence.

Administrative/Sales and Marketing Officer

4TSM Farms (Organic Fresh Protein Plaza) Akobo, Ibadan

Jan. 2018 - June 2018

Key Responsibilities/Achievements:

- Processed comprehensive expense reports and approve expenses on behalf of executives.
- Prepared PowerPoint presentations, create Excel spreadsheet reports, gather and distribute confidential reports.
- Created a valuable relationship and critical link between internal/external customers and management team
- Conducted market research to evaluate trends and competition ventures
- Monitored progress of sales through various methods
- Kept records of sales, invoices and support documents.

Administrative Officer (NYSC)

College of Education, Agricultural Education Dept., Benin City

Jan. 2017 - Dec. 2017

Key Responsibilities:

- Monitored and maintained office equipment and inventory supplies; orders replacement supplies as needed
- Updated office policies and procedures, scheduled calendar and updated as needed
- Preparing reports on expenses, office budgets, and other expenditures
- Organizing special functions and social events
- Preparing correspondence, documentation, or presentation materials

EDUCATION

B.Tech. (Hons.) Animal Production and Health (Second Class Upper Division)

Ladoke Akintola University of Technology Ogbomoso, Oyo State

2010-2015

Senior Secondary School Certificate

United Comprehensive College Ogbomoso, Oyo State.

2002-2008

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS/ TRAINING

International Project Management Professionals

(June, 2017)

Certified Fabrics distributor at klassique_fabrics

(Currently)

SKILLS AND ATTRIBUTES

- Demonstrated expertise in decision making and policy formulation.
- Microsoft Office Suite Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, Operating System: Windows 7, 8, 10
- Problem-solving, analytical thinking and multi-tasking skills to enhance service delivery
- Excellent written and verbal communication skills
- Excellent time management skills; ability to prioritize

- Willingness to learn and to grow with the company and motivated to take on additional projects and solve problems
- Self-directed and able to work without supervision
- Comfortable in both a leadership and team-player role, manages team members, leads assistant meetings, and supervises when needed

HOBBIES: Reading, Traveling, surfing the internet, playing volleyball, socializing with people.

REFEERES

To be provided on request